mobisoftinfotech.com 2019-06-10

# Privacy policy - Mobisoft Infotech

We at Mobisoft Infotech are committed to protecting your privacy. This policy provides you with the details of how any personal data we collect from you or that you provide us will be used and processed. We periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice by sending you an email notification.

### Consent

Mobisoft Infotech privacy policy describes how we collect and use information in connection with your access to and use of our website and any of its subdomains, mobile applications, and related services (collectively, the ‘Services’).

By accessing and/or using any of our Services, you accept and signify your informed consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

### Who We Are

We are Mobisoft Infotech LLC. We are a global technology company with offices in India and USA.

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act (‘DPA’) and in-line with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the ‘GDPR’), Mobisoft Infotech is the ‘Data Controller’ and is responsible for your personal data.

If you have any concerns about the way we use your information or any questions about this Privacy Policy, please let us know. We can be contacted via email at info@mobisoftinfotech.com

### Information We Collect

You are free to explore the Websites without providing any Personal Information about yourself. When you visit the Website or register for the Subscription Service, we request that you provide Personal Information about yourself, and we collect Navigational Information.

We may collect and process the following aspects of data about you:

Information that you provide us– this is information you give us by filling in forms on our website or by corresponding with us by phone, email or otherwise or by applying for jobs via our website.

When You Visit our Website- whenever you visit our website, we will automatically collect technical information and information about your visit.

"Personal Information"

This refers to any information that you voluntarily submit to us and that identifies you personally, including contact information, such as your name, e-mail address, company name, address, phone number, and other information about yourself or your business. Personal Information can also include information about you that is available on the internet, such as from Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and Google, or publicly available information that we acquire from service providers.

Personal Information also includes Navigational Information where such information can directly or indirectly identify an individual. Navigational information refers to information about your computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit, and pages viewed. Except for this, we do not collect Sensitive Information from you.

### Log Files

When you use our services or view content provided by us, we automatically collect information about your computer hardware and software. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, internet service provider (ISP), the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, clickstream data, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Mobisoft Infotech for the operation of the Subscription Service, to maintain the quality of the Subscription Service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Mobisoft Infotech Website. For these purposes, we do link this automatically-collected data to Personal Information such as name, email address, address, and phone number.

### Information we collect from third parties

From time to time, we may receive Personal Information about you from third party sources including partners with which we offer co-branded services or engage in joint marketing activities and publicly available sources such as social media websites.

### Information About Children

The Websites are not intended for or targeted at children under 16, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 16 If you believe that we have collected information about a child under 16, please contact us at info@mobisoftinfotech.com, so that we may delete the information.

### What we do with your information

We use the information held about you in the following ways:

  * To ensure that content from our website is presented in the most effective way for you and your computer;
  * To carry out any requests or obligations arising from any contact you may have with us;
  * To provide you with information or services that you have requested from us or which we feel may interest you, if you have given us consent to get in contact with you;
  * To enable you to participate in any interactive features our service offers, as and when you choose to do so;
  * To consider any job applicants;
  * To notify you of any changes to our service.

### Compliance with Our Privacy Policy

We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy. Customers who subscribe to our Subscription Services are obligated through our agreements with them to comply with this Privacy Policy.

### We Never Sell Personal Information

We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party.

### Use of Personal Information

In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to:

  * Improve your browsing experience by personalizing the Websites and to improve the Subscription Service;
  * Send information or Mobisoft Infotech content to you which we think may be of interest to you by post, email, or other means and send you marketing communications relating to our business;
  * Promote the use of our services to you and share promotional and information content with you in accordance with your communication preferences;
  * Provide other companies with statistical information about our users -- but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;
  * Send information to you regarding changes to our Customer Terms of Service, Privacy Policy (including the Cookie Policy), or other legal agreements
  * Meet legal requirements.

We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, we do not transfer your Personal Information to the third party.

We use the information collected through our Subscription Service by our customers for the following purposes:

  * To provide the Subscription Service (which may include the detection, prevention, and resolution of security and technical issues);
  * To respond to customer support requests;
  * Otherwise to fulfill the obligations under the Mobisoft Infotech Customer Terms of Service.

### Legal basis for processing Personal Information (EEA visitors only)

If you are a visitor/customer located in the European Economic Area ("EEA"), Mobisoft Infotech LLC is the data controller of your personal information. Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will normally collect personal information from you only where we have your consent to do so, where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you.

If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information). Similarly, if we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.

### Technical Information

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system, and browser type for system administration. This is only statistical data and does not identify any individual.

We also collect details of your visits to our website in the form of analytics, this could include places and resources you access on our site, time spent on our site, and where you are directed to our site from.

### Use of Navigational Information

We use Navigational Information to operate and improve the Websites and the Subscription Service. We may also use Navigational Information alone or in combination with Personal Information to provide you with personalized information about Mobisoft Infotech.

### Customer Testimonials and Comments

We post customer testimonials and comments on our Websites, which may contain Personal Information. We obtain each customer's consent via email prior to posting the customer's name and testimonial.

### Security of your Personal Information

We take the security of your personal data very seriously and have policies and procedures in place to ensure our compliance with the DPA and GDPR. We secure the Personal Information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. All Personal Information is protected using appropriate physical, technical, and organizational measures.

### Social Media Features

Our Websites include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share This button. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.

### External Websites

Our Websites provide links to other websites. We do not control and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these other websites. Our provision of such links does not constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these other websites, which are subject to any privacy and other policies they may have.

### Public Forums

We offer publicly accessible message boards, blogs, and community forums. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose any information through our public message boards, blogs, or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. We will correct or delete any information you have posted on the Websites if you so request, as described in "Opting Out and Unsubscribing" below.

### Retention of Personal Information

How long we keep the information we collect about you depends on the type of information. as described in further detail below. After such time, we will either delete or anonymize your information or, if this is not possible, then we will securely store your information and isolate it from any further use until deletion is possible.

We retain Personal Information that you provide to us where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, as long as is required in order to contact you about the Subscription Service or our other services, or as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements).

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your Personal Information, we securely delete the information or anonymize it or, if this is not possible, then we will securely store your Personal Information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible. We will delete this information from the servers at an earlier date if you so request.

If you provide information to our customers as part of their use of the Subscription Service, our customers decide how long to retain the personal information they collect from you. If a customer terminates its use of the Subscription Service, then we will provide the customer with access to all information stored for the customer by the Subscription Service, including any Personal Information provided by you, for export by the customer according to our agreement with our customer. After termination, we may, unless legally prohibited, delete all customer information, including your Personal Information, from the Subscription Service.

If you have elected to receive marketing communications from us, we retain information about your marketing preferences for a reasonable period of time from the date you last expressed interest in our content, products, or services, such as when you last opened an email from us. We retain information derived from cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time from the date such information was created.

### Disclosure of your information

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your data in order to comply with any legal obligation.

We use third-party selected service providers including IT and system management services, legal and financial advisors, billing and payment processing services, fraud detection and prevention services, web analytics, marketing services, recruitment services, content providers and HM Revenue & Customs, regulators and other authorities (collectively, “Third Party Service(s)”)

We may also disclose your information to third parties to whom we may choose to sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets. Alternatively, we may seek to acquire other businesses or merge with them. If a change happens to our business, then the new owners may use your personal data in the same way as set out in this Privacy Policy.

We require all Third Party Services to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our Third Party Services to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

### Third Party links

Our website may from time to time contain links to and from other websites. If you were to follow a link to any of these sites please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and we do accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please make sure to check these policies before you submit any personal data to any of these websites.

### Your rights

You have the right to find out about what information we hold about you. If you wish to access and/or request us to make corrections to the personal information that you have stored with us, please contact us via email to info@mobisoftinfotech.com.

You also have the right ‘to be forgotten’ and to have your information permanently deleted from our systems. Again if you would like to exercise this right then contact us at the email address above.

There will be no charge for reasonable electronic access to your information or for your right to be forgotten.

### Cookies

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

### What is a cookie?

Cookies are small files comprised of letters and numbers that are downloaded onto your desktop computer, mobile, or other handheld devices when you access certain websites. Cookies allow a website to recognize a user’s device and help your browser navigate through the website by allowing you to log in automatically by remembering settings you selected during earlier visits, amongst other functions. Cookies do not harm your computer.

### The use of cookies on this website

Cookies help us provide you with a good experience when you browse this website and allow you to make full use of the features available on this website. We do not use cookies to collect or record information such as your name, address or personal details.

We use cookies on our website for one purpose, and that is to collect statistical information about how visitors use our website, so we can improve the way this website works and measure our success. By recording such statistics as browser usage, visitor location, operating system etc. we can measure and improve on how we manage and maintain our site, in order to give you an ultimately better visitor experience.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. Unless you have adjusted your browser settings so that it will refuse cookies, cookies will be set when you access our website. By continuing to use and browse this website, you agree and consent to our use of cookies. If you do not consent, please understand that certain features of our website may not function as intended.

### Individual cookies we use

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to understand general trends in our content and traffic sources such as where users come from and which pages are most popular.

### Facebook

The Facebook button allows you to share our platform with your friends and other Facebook users.

### Twitter

This button allows you to share our platform and services with your followers.

### LinkedIn

We use this button to allow you to share our platform and the services we offer with your connections.

### To Unsubscribe From Our Communications

You may unsubscribe from our marketing communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of our emails, updating your communication preferences, or by sending us an email at info@mobisoftinfotech.com. Attention: Privacy. Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with us or the Subscription Service.

### To Unsubscribe from Our Customers' Communications

Our customers are solely responsible for their own marketing emails and other communications; we cannot unsubscribe you from their communications. You can unsubscribe from our customers' marketing communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of their emails, or by contacting them directly.

### Changes to Privacy Policy and your duty to inform us of changes

Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy will be displayed on this page and where appropriate notified to you via email.

It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during your relationship with us.
